limkokwing.net 2019-04-27

# Privacy Policy @ Limkokwing University of Creative Technology

### Login

Thinking of enrolling at Limkokwing? Login with your account to enquire and register online.

Create a new accountWhy register

Forgot Password?

### Forgot Password

Back to login

### Login

Thinking of enrolling at Limkokwing? Login with your account to enquire and register online.

I already have an account

### Create new Account

  * Terms of Use
  * Privacy Policy
  * Personal Data Protection

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy (the “Policy”) outlines the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by Limkokwing University of Creative Technology (“Limkokwing”) when you use this website located at www.limkokwing.net, and all associated, subsidiary and affiliated websites linked to www.limkokwing.net by Limkokwing (collectively, the “Website”).

Limkokwing reserves the right to modify the Policy at any time without prior notice. By continuing to access the Website after such modifications have been published you signify your agreement to such modified Policy.

### Information Collection & Use

There are a number of situations in which personal information may be collected from you. We do not share this information collected from the Website with third parties.

#### Feedback and Enquiry

We collect information including, but not limited, to your name, mailing address, phone number and email address when you register an account at the Website, making enquiries, signup for newsletters/updates, participating in contests and sending us feedbacks.

#### Course Registration

If you register for courses, we require that you provide certain personal, identification information, including, but not limited, to your personal information, guardian information, academic information and your credit card information. This information is necessary for us to process your registration and for us to get in touch with you.

#### Statistics Analysis

We also collect information about your computer and about your visits to and use of the Website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, Internet service provider, operating system, length of visit and page views. This information generated, which does not identify individual users, is used to generate statistics and reports about the Website usage by using JavaScripts, which do not store any personal identifiable information on users’ computers.

### Limkokwing Facebook App

The following statements published by Limkokwing University of Creative Technology (LUCT) apply to content provided by you through your use of the Limkokwing Facebook app (the "App").

As a registered Facebook user, you are also subject to Facebook's privacy policy. Please check your Facebook account privacy settings for further information.

#### About the App

The App lets you access particular online services using your Facebook login.

#### Sharing your information with us and others

When you first access the App, you will be presented with a Facebook permissions page, which will advise you about the Facebook information you will be sharing with the App and other Facebook users. You can then decide whether or not to share your Facebook information by using the App. If you decide not to grant permission you will not be able to use the App.

By granting permission, you will be agreeing to share your Facebook user details (your name, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID and any other information you choose to share according to your Facebook account settings) as well as the user details of your Facebook friends, and information about your use of the App.

If you choose to post content or other data on the App, for example, this can be accessed by all of your Facebook friends.

#### Collecting and using your information

When you use the App, you provide us with basic personal and contact information: (a) your name (b) email address (c) information you provide us when you contact us for help; (d) information you enter into our system when using the App. (e) Facebook profile picture

We may use the information you provided us to contact your from time to time to provide you with important information, required notices and marketing promotions.

User Provided Information – The App obtains the information you provide when you use the App.

Automatically Collected Information – In addition, the App may collect certain info automatically, such as your IP address, the type of Internet browser you use, and information about the way you use the App.

This App does not collect precise information about your location.

#### Third party access to information obtained by this App

We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. 

We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;
  * with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement.
  * if LUCT is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information;
  * to advertisers and third party advertising networks and analytics companies as described below under the Section entitled Automatic Data Collection and Advertising.

#### Unsubscribing

To unsubscribe, remove the App by accessing the application settings in your Facebook account settings.

Once you remove the App, we no longer have permission to access your Facebook information and your data will be removed from the App.

#### Data retention policy, managing your information 

We will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the App and for a reasonable time thereafter. If you'd like us to delete User Provided Data that you have provided via the App, please contact us and we will respond in a reasonable time.

Please note that some or all of the User Provided Data may be required in order for the App to function properly, and we may be required to retain certain information by law.

#### Automatic data collection and advertising

We may work with analytics companies to help us understand how the App is being used, such as the frequency and duration of usage.

### Feedback and Enquiry

We welcome any questions, comments or concerns you might have with regard to your privacy when using the Website. If you have any questions about the Policy or our treatment of your personal data, please notify us.
